bigmarketresearch.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Big Market Research**

Big Market Research is committed to protecting the clients personal information and credentials. With due regard, the company introduces new and updated policy statement occasionally as and when new uses of information, new products and services are developed and new technologies are deployed. On 25th May 2018, the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) launched by EU replaced the existing 1995 European Data Protection Directive. Owing to the advancements in digital era and the introduction of GDPR, we have come up with a more comprehensive version of our privacy laws, modernized to resonate with todays fast paced data-driven world.

Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy explains Big Market Researchs (we, us or our)strategic approach towards the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of the users information by the company. It summarizes the various ways we acquire and treat your Data when you access, visit and/or use the Service. It also governs your Data that we may acquire offline. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected on sites, applications, destinations, or services linked to from the Service that we do not own or control.

 **Collection and Use of information**

Big Market Research is involved in the process of assessing the viability of a new good or service through research conducted directly with the consumer. This practice allows our customers to discover the target market and record opinions and other input from consumers regarding interest in the product. The company collects the quantitative market data through research and interviews, and thus, the data may fluctuate due to changes in the market conditions. It is not responsible for any false or misleading information provided by users or manufacturers.

Other data that we collect is extensively, but not limited to, your basic personal and navigational information. When you register for our services or newsletters, youre requested to provide a few of your personal data such as, name, email and contact details. Such information that you provide to us when signing-up for or maintaining an account, registering for any event with us or otherwise receiving a service from us, is stored temporarily with your consent to improve on the websites user experience. Also, when you purchase any entity through our website, the required credentials will be stored in the secure servers and systems owned and managed by Big Market Research.

 **Information collected by automated means**

We might automatically some of your information as you navigate through our website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, unique browser identifiers, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies. We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities (traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data) over time and across third-party websites or other online services (i.e. behavioral tracking). The information we collect automatically helps us to improve our website and to deliver a better and more personalized service.

 **Cookie Policy**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computers hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps in analyzing the web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. We use cookies to administer the website, store visitor preferences, record session information, which helps us to improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users.

A cookie does not necessarily give us any access to your personal files over your computer, or any information other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies by choosing the viable option in the dialog box that appears when you visit a website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Based on the data acquired from cookies, we are able to direct our visitors to new areas that they might be interested in. It also helps us to customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and we take care that a user is not sent the same banner ad repeatedly.

 **Compliance to Privacy Laws**

Big Market Research is committed to respecting the users right to confidentiality. We abide by all the current government laws and regulations, and we recognize our obligations in continuously updating and expanding our measures to keep-up with the demands of the newly introduced GDPR. You can read about our GDPR compliance [here](https://www.bigmarketresearch.com/gdpr-policy).

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personal information (including sensitive personal information).

 **Disclaimer**

The company takes utmost care to ensure that the information provided on the website is relevant and accurate. However, it does not provide any warranty, undertakings, or representations about the authenticity of the content on the website. It takes no responsibility if the client suffers any loss or damage due to the usage of the information on the website.

The companys website includes certain links that will take you to third party websites. However, it is not responsible and administer no control over the content on the websites. Such links are for general purposes only, and do not endorse any material on these websites or any association with their operators. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

 **Copyright Notice**

The content on the companys website is copyright- Big Market Research All rights reserved.

The client may print or download extracts from the website for personal use only. Apart from subsequent viewing purposes and personal use, they should not make use of any of the material stored on any medium.

Any resale, disclosure, lending, or reproduction of service or publication can only be made with the prior written permission from Big Market Research.

Transmission and/or reproduction of any part from the website, by any means or in any form (whether photocopying, mechanical, electronic, recording or otherwise) are prohibited without prior written permission.

 **Policy Changes**

The company may come up with a new and updated policy statement occasionally by posting a revised version of the statement on the website. Kindly refer to this page frequently to check for the policy amendments, if any.
